<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.0.xsd">

    <changeSet author="author" id="1">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (0,
            '• Are there any parts of the city where you live which you are afraid to visit after dark? Where?\n• Are
            there certain weather conditions that scare people? What are they? Why do people become scared?\n• Are you
            afraid of flying?\n• Are you afraid of ghosts?\n• Are you afraid of giving a speech in public?\n• Are you
            afraid of going to the dentist?\n• Are you afraid of heights?\n• Are you afraid of the dark?\n• Are you
            afraid of getting old? Why?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Fears');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (0,
            '• Why do people volunteer?\n• Would you like to work as a volunteer?\n• Have you ever done any volunteer
            work?\n• Is volunteering worth the time it takes?\n• Why would you enjoy volunteering?\n• Do you know anyone
            who has done volunteer work?\n• Have you ever benefitted by someone\'s volunteer work?\n• What benefits do
            you get personally by volunteering?\n• Can you list some reasons why people volunteer?\n• What types of
            volunteer work would be unpleasant for you?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Volunteer work');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (0,
            '• What ganre of music do you prefer?\n• Do you think the ganre you listen to influences your state of mind
            and mood?\n• Do you listen to music while working or studying?\n• Have you slept with music?\n• Why is
            classical music so popular?\n• What is more important in a song:the lyrics or the melody?\n• Remember and
            tell about the last consert you\'ve attended\n• Do you think it\'s unacceptable to lip-sync?\n• Is music
            made on computer worse than usual one?\n• Do you sing whilst taking shower?\n• Could you imagine your life
            without music?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Music');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (0,
            '• How do you feel about advertising?\n• Are you easily persuaded to buy something after seeing or hearing
            an advertisement?\n• What kind of advertisements attracts your attention?\n• What’s the best advertisement
            you\’ve ever seen?\n• What’s the most shocking advertisement you\’ve ever seen?\n• What’s the funniest
            advertisement you\’ve ever seen?\n• What makes an advertisement memorable?\n• Is advertising an art?\n• Can
            your favorite celebrity to persuade you to buy a product?\n• Are children and teenagers more influenced with
            advertising than adults?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Advertising');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(0,
            '• What is work-life balance for you?\n• Is there a “long-hours” working culture in your country?\n• Why
            should employers care about their employees’ work-life balance?\n• Can you tell me about your working day
            routine?\n• What does your company do to help you maintain work-life balance?\n• Do you overtime? If you
            have urgent task will you overtime or portpone it the next day?\n• Have you spent all your annual leave for
            the previous year? Do you prefer to spend it or get compensation for unused days?\n• What is the best time
            to work? Do you prefer to start work earlier or later?\n• Have you ever worked shifts? Did you enjoy it? Why
            / why not?\n• What do you think are the pros and cons of working shifts?\n• Do you think working shifts
            could be bad for your health? Why / why not?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Work-life balance');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(0,
            '• Are you good at making friends?\n• Can you remember your first friend?\n• What’s the best age for making
            friends?\n• How long has your strongest friendship lasted?\n• How often do you contact with your
            long-distance friends?\n• How difficult is it to maintain a friendship?\n• What can break a good
            relationship?\n• Is it a good idea to go on holiday with a friend?\n• What do you think about
            lending/borrowing money to/from a friend?\n• Would it be difficult if your friend was your boss or
            subordinate?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Friends 2');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(0,
            '• Are you easily persuaded to buy something after seeing or hearing an advertisement?\n• What kind of
            advertisements attracts your attention?\n• What’s the best advertisement you’ve ever seen?\n• What’s the
            most shocking advertisement you’ve ever seen?\n• What’s the funniest advertisement you’ve ever seen?\n• What
            makes an advertisement memorable?\n• Is advertising an art?\n• Can your favorite celebrity to persuade you
            to buy a product?\n• Are children and teenagers more influenced with advertising than adults?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Friends 1');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (participant_limit, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(0,
            '• How do you feel about advertising?\n• Are you easily persuaded to buy something after seeing or hearing
            an advertisement?\n• What kind of advertisements attracts your attention?\n• What’s the best advertisement
            you\’ve ever seen?\n• What’s the most shocking advertisement you\’ve ever seen?\n• What’s the funniest
            advertisement you\’ve ever seen?\n• What makes an advertisement memorable?\n• Is advertising an art?\n• Can
            your favorite celebrity to persuade you to buy a product?\n• Are children and teenagers more influenced with
            advertising than adults?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Health');
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

    <changeSet id="3" author="brokorenko" runOnChange="true">
        <comment>Upload 3 meeting_info</comment>
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO meeting_info (questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES ('? What are two disadvantages of using smartphones and tablets?? What do you think about Cybercafes?
            are
            they still useful?? Do you like a job in which you have to use computers?? Do you spend too much time
            online??
            Does your mother of father know how to use a computer?? Do computers make life easier?? What websites do you
            visit in a regular basis?? What do you think about the Apple?? What are some advantages of using social
            networks?? Do you visit English websites?', 'ADVANCED', 'Internet and Computers');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (' How does having children change someones life?
            1. What kinds of things do people have to give up when they have children?
            2. What are some of the benefits of having children?
            3. Do you think it is better to have children when you are older or younger?
            4. What is the best number of children to have? How many boys or girls?
            5. What do you think about "childfree"?
            6. Do you want to have children?
            - If not: Why not? Have you told your parents about your decision? What do they think about it?
            - If so: When do you want to have children and how many do you want to have?
            7. Do you want your first child to be a boy or a girl? Why?
            8. How do children who have no brothers or sisters act?
            9. What do you think about kids from a childrens home? Would you take a child from an orphanage? ',
            'INTERMEDIATE', 'Having children');

            INSERT INTO meeting_info (questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES ('1. Are you good at making friends?
            2. Can you remember your first friend?
            3. Whats the best age for making friends?
            4. How long has your strongest friendship lasted?
            5. How often do you contact with your long-distance friends?
            6. How difficult is it to maintain a friendship?
            7. What can break a good relationship?
            8. Is it a good idea to go on holiday with a friend?
            9. What do you think about lending/borrowing money to/from a friend?
            10. Would it be difficult if your friend was your boss or subordinate?
            11. Is it a good idea to start business with a friend?
            12. Is it possible to establish a strong friendship through the Internet?
            13. Is it possible to have the best friend from a different generation?
            14. Is it possible to have the best friend from a different social or cultural background?
            15. Is it possible to have the best friend of the opposite sex without falling in love?
            16. Describe your ideal girlfriend/boyfriend.
            17. Is it possible to be friends with an ex-spouse?
            18. Is it possible to be friends with your teacher?
            19. Can you imagine your life without friends? ',
            'INTERMEDIATE', 'Friends');
        </sql>
    </changeSet>

</databaseChangeLog>