<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-3.0.xsd">

    <changeSet author="author" id="10">
        <sql>
            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (1,
            'Are there any parts of the city where you live which you are afraid to visit after dark? Where?;Are there certain weather conditions that scare people? What are they? Why do people become scared?;Are you afraid of flying?;Are you afraid of ghosts?;Are you afraid of giving a speech in public?;Are you afraid of going to the dentist?;Are you afraid of heights?;Are you afraid of the dark?;Are you afraid of getting old? Why?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Fears v.1');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (2,
            'Are there any numbers that people are afraid of in your culture?;Were you afraid of the dark as a child?;What animal do you think is the most scary?;What is the scariest movie you have ever seen?;What is your biggest fear in life? Are you afraid that it might come true?;Do you believe people can be cured of phobias by hypnosis?;Are you afraid of speaking English?;A foreign language?;In front of many people?;At official functions?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Fears v.2');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (3,
            'Why do people volunteer?;Would you like to work as a volunteer?;Have you ever done any volunteer work?;Is volunteering worth the time it takes?;Why would you enjoy volunteering?;Do you know anyone who has done volunteer work?;Have you ever benefitted by someone\'s volunteer work?;What benefits do you get personally by volunteering?;Can you list some reasons why people volunteer?;What types of volunteer work would be unpleasant for you?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Volunteer work');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (4,
            'What ganre of music do you prefer?;Do you think the ganre you listen to influences your state of mind and mood?;Do you listen to music while working or studying?;Have you slept with music?;Why is classical music so popular?;What is more important in a song:the lyrics or the melody?;Remember and tell about the last consert you\'ve attended;Do you think it\'s unacceptable to lip-sync?;Is music made on computer worse than usual one?;Do you sing whilst taking shower?;Could you imagine your life without music?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Music');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES (5,
            'How do you feel about advertising?;Are you easily persuaded to buy something after seeing or hearing an advertisement?;What kind of advertisements attracts your attention?;What’s the best advertisement you\’ve ever seen?;What’s the most shocking advertisement you\’ve ever seen?;What’s the funniest advertisement you\’ve ever seen?;What makes an advertisement memorable?;Is advertising an art?;Can your favorite celebrity to persuade you to buy a product?;Are children and teenagers more influenced with advertising than adults?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Advertising');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(6,
            'What is work-life balance for you?;Is there a “long-hours” working culture in your country?;Why should employers care about their employees’ work-life balance?;Can you tell me about your working day routine?;What does your company do to help you maintain work-life balance?;Do you overtime? If you have urgent task will you overtime or portpone it the next day?;Have you spent all your annual leave for the previous year? Do you prefer to spend it or get compensation for unused days?;What is the best time to work? Do you prefer to start work earlier or later?;Have you ever worked shifts? Did you enjoy it? Why / why not?;What do you think are the pros and cons of working shifts?;Do you think working shifts could be bad for your health? Why / why not?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Work-life balance');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(7,
            'Are you good at making friends?;Can you remember your first friend?;What’s the best age for making friends?;How long has your strongest friendship lasted?;How often do you contact with your long-distance friends?;How difficult is it to maintain a friendship?;What can break a good relationship?;Is it a good idea to go on holiday with a friend?;What do you think about lending/borrowing money to/from a friend?;Would it be difficult if your friend was your boss or subordinate?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Friends v.1');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(8,
            'Is it a good idea to start business with a friend?;Is it possible to establish a strong friendship through the Internet?;Is it possible to have the best friend from a different generation?;Is it possible to have the best friend from a different social or cultural background?;Is it possible to have the best friend of the opposite sex without falling in love?;Describe your ideal girlfriend/boyfriend.;Is it possible to be friends with an ex-spouse?;Is it possible to be friends with your teacher?;Can you imagine your life without friends?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Friends v.2');


            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(9,
            'How conscious are you about your health?;What things might damage your health?;Should you give up something to protect your health?;What do you do to stay healthy?;Do you ever read articles or watch TV programmes about health?;Do you usually take medicine when you are sick?;Do you usually go to a doctor when you get a cold?;How often do you have a health check?;What are your experiences of hospitals?;Have you ever been to a hospital in another country?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Health v.1');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(10,
            'Is being gay more difficult in some countries than others?;In your opinion, can a gay be a religious person?;What main problems do gays have in the military?;In what ways does the gay community try to tackle homophobia? Are they being successful?;Do you think being lesbian is viewed as being worse, the same or better than being gay in our society?;Could you name any famous lesbian through history?;Do you believe gays and heterosexuals have the same rights? Do they have equal duties?;What\'s your opinion on gay marriage?;What do you think of adoption by gay couples?;Do you think homosexual families can bring up children as well as straight families? If not, why?;What stereotypes do you know about gays?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Gay Community v.1');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(11,
            'What problems do you think someone goes through when they find out they are gay?;Do you think they should try to change?;In your opinion, should they say they are gay?;What do you think your parents\' reaction would be if you told them you are gay?;Do you think one of them would take it better / worse?;Do you think their first reaction would persist or would it change?;How about your best friend\'s reaction?;How would you react if one of your children told you they\'re gay?;What are the main problems gays have to face at college?;Is it easier for a gay to live in a village or in a city?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Gay Community v.2');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(12,
            'About how many of them would you say are not offensive?;How is it being gay in your country?;Do you know anyone who is gay?;How about any celebrities?;Or any historical figure?;Are there any gay characters on a current TV series?;Could you tell us about them?;What\'s the meaning of "homophobia"?;In your view, is there homophobia in our society? If not, why?;Do you believe that the gay community is being discriminated against in any way?;If so, why do you think there is such discrimination?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Gay Community v.3');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(13,
            'How does having children change someone\’s life?;What kinds of things do people have to give up when they have children?;What are some of the benefits of having children?;Do you think it is better to have children when you are older or younger?;What is the best number of children to have? How many boys or girls?;What do you think about "childfree"?;Do you want to have children?;If not: Why not? Have you told your parents about your decision? What do they think about it?;If so: When do you want to have children and how many do you want to have?;Do you want your first child to be a boy or a girl? Why?;How do children who have no brothers or sisters act?;What do you think about kids from a children\'s home? Would you take a child from an orphanage?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Having children');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(14,
            'What are two disadvantages of using smartphones and tablets?;What do you think about Cybercafes? Are they still useful?;Do you like a job in which you have to use computers?;Do you spend too much time online?;Does your mother of father know how to use a computer?;Do computers make life easier?;What websites do you visit in a regular basis?;What do you think about the Apple?;What are some advantages of using social networks?;Do you visit English websites?',
            'INTERMEDIATE',
            'Internet and Computers');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(15,
            'Do you often go to job interview?;Do you like it?;What is the reason for you to go?;Do you use English for interview?;Have you ever interview another people?;What about the most interesting interview?;How was the most stressful interview?;Tell about the most strange interview?;How do you prepare yourself for interview?;What is your attitude to online interview?',
            'PRE_INTERMEDIATE',
            'Job interview1');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(16,
            'Do you often go to job interview?;Do you like it?;What is the reason for you to go?;Do you use English for interview?;Have you ever interview another people?;What about the most interesting interview?;How was the most stressful interview?;Tell about the most strange interview?;How do you prepare yourself for interview?;What is your attitude to online interview?',
            'PRE_INTERMEDIATE',
            'Job interview');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(17,
            'How could hospitals be made better places to visit and stay in?;Which is better: private and public health care?;What do you think about alternative medicine?;Who is more responsible for your health: you or the government?;Do you normally go one doctor in particular or any available doctor?;What disease frightens you the most? Why?;What do you do to stay healthy?',
            'PRE_INTERMEDIATE',
            'Health v.2');

            INSERT INTO meeting_catalog (id, questions, speaking_level, topic)
            VALUES(18,
            'Do you have a lot of free time?;\'Time is money\'. Do you agree or disagree?;What\'s your perception of time now?;Do you show up early or late for work/university/meeting with friends?;Are you a \'night owl\' or an \'early bird\'?;Do you use any time management apps to structure your day/week?;Do you have some tips on how to organize your day for maximum productivity?;What Is procrastination? Why we do it and how to stop it);What would you do if you had a few extra hours in a day?;Does time go by slowly or quickly for you? What does this depend on?;What is your ideal working schedule?;Have you ever had some situations when procrastination was good for you?',
            'PRE_INTERMEDIATE',
            'Time');
        </sql>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>